隔板
Bulkhead
你我二人在这个鬼地方居然也会相遇
imagine you and I bumping into each other in the middle of
都怪那个该死的能量信号
nowhere while tracking a stray energon signal.
没错 打击
Yea, Breakdown
今天是你的幸运日
it must be your lucky day.
你的人类小宠物在哪儿？
Where is your pet human?
等我消灭你之后 再去拜访她如何？
How about when I finish with you, I'll pay her a visit?
戳到你的软肋了么？
So the wrecker's got a soft spot.
短暂的重逢让我终生难忘…
As much as I'll miss our little reunions...
这一锤送你上路！
... hammer time.
长官 以我们现有的运力 只能带走一个
Sir, we only have the resources to transport one.
带走那个打赢的
Take the victor.
“马可” “马可”
Marco. Marco.
“马可”！
Marco!
神子？
Miko?
哼…你应该接着说“波罗”！
Hmmm... You're supposed to say "Polo"!
呃？
Eh?
神子 跟救护车说 我需要环陆桥
Miko, let Ratchet know I need a Ground Bridge.
单枪匹马独自迎敌 只是匹夫之勇 隔板
Engaging the enemy on your own was foolish, Bulkhead.
打击偷袭我
Breakdown jumped me.
我就知道他不行 啊！
I knew I could take 'em. Ugha!
别乱动
Stay still.
看那家伙的惨状就知道了 对吧 小隔？
But we should see the other guy, right, Bulk?
呃 对了 关于这个…
Uh, yea, about that...
你没能消灭他？
You didn't torch him?
不完全是
Not exactly.
我以为是你们干的
I figured you all did.
哦…
Oh...
我醒来时 打击已经…不在了
When I came to, Breakdown was, just gone.
我记得有直升机的声音
I remember hearing a copter.
可能是福勒探员把他带走了？
Maybe it was Agent Fowler?
不是我
Not me.
但我猜到是谁了
But I have an idea who.
告诉我“绑虎事件”发生的位置
Show me where this Con-napping occurred.
威震天陛下
Lord Megatron
打击现在下落不明
I fear Breakdown has gone missing.
是汽车人干的吗？
The Autobots?
根据那个精准无比的声波 提供的监视资料
According to surveillance provided by the astonishingly accurate Soundwave
绑架打击的是人类
Breakdown was abducted by humans.
你想说什么？
You point?
我强烈建议
My strongest recommendation
组建一支救援队 把那群自讨苦吃的害虫消灭干净！
we assemble a rescue team to hunt the vermin responsible for this outrage.
让打击自生自灭吧
Breakdown is on his own.
啊？呃…
Hah? Eh...
主人的意思是？
Master?
如果打击轻易落在比他弱小的人类手中
If Breakdown allowed himself to be captured by those smaller than him
weaker than him
那只能说他气数已尽了
he deserves whatever fate awaits him.
但少了打击这个核心成员 我们…
But Breakdown is a key player in our, eh...
您的智慧毋庸置疑 威震天陛下…
Your wisdom reigns supreme, Lord Megatron...
…暂时的
... for now.
什么？
What?
肮脏的肉球！
Filthy fleshlings
你以为你们是谁？
who do you think you are?
我们是机械党
We are MECH
而我 就是塞拉斯
and I, am Silas.
立即放了我 我可以留你们一条生路
Release me now and I will let you live.
抱歉 对我们而言 你可是无价之宝
I'm afraid you are far too valuable to us.
呵呵 威震天从来不付赎金
Hehe, Megatron will never pay a ransom.
哦 你误会了
Oh, you misunderstand.
我们要的不是赎金
We don't want a ransom.
而是你
We want only you.
你的整个身体
All of you.
这就是我们发现隔板的地方
This is where we picked up Bulkhead.
位于俄罗斯东部的堪察加半岛
The Kamchatka Peninsula in Eastern Russia.
二十年前首次火山喷发后 大部分地区被遗弃
Much of it was abandoned twenty years ago when its volcano first erupted.
我有情报 今天早些时候 那里曾有机械党出没
My intel reported MECH activity there earlier today.
机械党？你是指那群技术狂人？
MECH? You mean those techy guys?
那些人知道我们就在这个星球上
The very ones who know of our existence on your planet.
他们一定跟踪了我们
They must have tracked one of us there.
但他们带走打击 目的何在？
But what would they want with Breakdown?
这有什么？让他们放心走吧
What's it matter? They can have him.
呵 是啊 被人类拖走了 哈！
Heh, yea. Dragged off by humans, Ha!
我也算是为人类做了善事 对吧？
Guess I softened him up for 'em, huh?
不害臊…
Nya...
救护车 重新激活环陆桥的上一个坐标
Ratchet, reactivate the previous Ground Bridge coordinates.
我们要营救打击
We will rescue Breakdown.
什么？
What?
擎天柱 你在开玩笑吧？
Optimus, you can't be serious.
机械党把他拆了才好呢
MECH can melt him down for all I care.
让虎子们自己去救人吧
Let the Cons rescue their own.
威震天从来不会在乎一个手下的性命
It is unlikely that Megatron would bother with an errand of mercy.
好吧 可我们干嘛要去救打击
OK. But this is Breakdown we are talking about.
有时候 为了顾全大局 我们必须看远一点
Sometimes we must rise above ourselves for the greater good.
噢 这话什么意思？
Oh, what's that supposed to mean?
打击会心怀感激 幡然悔悟 然后弃暗投明？
Breakdown's gotta be grateful and go all soft and join the cause?
尽管霸天虎改邪归正的可能性不大
While it is unlikely that any Decepticon will choose the path of good
但他们毕竟有改变命运的潜力
even they possess the potential for change.
切！我就知道你又要说教了
Neh! I knew where this was headed.
我说的顾全大局
By greater good
是指人类
I meant human kind.
机械党是目前最明确的威胁
MECH presents a clear and present danger.
擎天柱说的对
Prime's right.
大个子
Two time.
机械党正四处搜取最具突破性的科技
We know MECH is obssessed with obtaining ground-breaking technology.
所以我们不能让塞博特恩生物科技
Which means we cannot allow Cybertronian biology
落入他们的手中
to fall into their hands.
开门见山
Full disclosure
我们打算把你肢解
we intend to pull you apart.
给你一个“打击”
Break you down
怎么说都行
if you will.
我们会利用所发现的一切 研发新一代武器
And we will utilize whatever we discover to develop a new generation of weaponary.
恐怕你不会活到解体完成
I'm afraid that you won't survive the process.
所以我要提前感谢你的无私奉献
So thank you in advance for your sacrifice.
机械党会牢记这份人情的
MECH is very much in your debt.
你正在犯一个天大的错误 小不点儿
You're making a very big mistake, little man.
我要把你干掉 让他们从地板上拼凑你的尸体！
When I'm finished with you, they'll have to scrape you off the floor!
你显然不会晕血
Since you evidently aren't squeamish
所以我让你观赏全程
I'll allow you to watch.
他的痛觉感受器都关闭了吗？
Are his pain receptors disabled?
很好 这样他就不会大呼小叫了
Good, then he won't make as much noise.
拆开他
Open him up.
别这样 小隔
Come on, Bulk
你应该一起去
you got to go with.
我就是不去
Don't wanna.
隔板
Bulkhead.
大哥 抱歉
Optimus, I'm sorry.
这种事我做不了
I just can't do it.
我支持你的选择
I support your choice.
- 什…什么？\N- 什么？
- Wh-wh-what?\N- What?
考虑到你和打击之间的恩怨
Given your history with Breakdown
你的判断力可能会受到影响
your judgement maybe clouded
这对任务有弊无利
and thus jeopardize the mission.
另外
Besides
那名霸天虎更需要的是医生 而不是战士
the Decepticon maybe more in need of a medic than another warrior.
我准备好了 擎天柱
Locked and loaded, Optimus.
汽车人 出发！
Autobots, roll out!
好吧 祝你们马到成功
Fine, happy hunting.
呃！
Uh!
呃 你想干点啥？
Uh, what do you see?
怪兽电影两集连放？
Creature double feature?
随便你
Sure.
哇哦 算我一个
Whooa, I'm in.
没有生命迹象
No signs of life.
人类和塞博特恩人的都没有
Human or Cybertronian.
别管那些胎痕了 大黄蜂
Forget the tracks, Bumblebee.
我收到一个微弱的能量信号 西北偏北方向 约四分钟路程
I'm picking up a faint energon signal three kliks north by northwest.
是打击
Breakdown.
但我们应该收不到他的信号 除非…
But we shouldn't be getting a reading, unless...
他的能量泄漏了
His energon's been spilled.
“哥斯拉大战五头猿”
Dinolizard vs. Five-Headed Ape
你要错过大场面了
you are missing the smack down.
不 错过大场面的是你
No, you are missing the smack down
气死我了
which stinks
打击是你的老对手
'cause Breakdown is your arch-enemy
不是擎天柱的
not Optimus's
更不是机械党的
and definitely not MECH's.
唉…神子 你不懂
Hugh... Miko, you don't understand.
打击和我
Breakdown and me
我们有很深的过节
we go way back.
你不知道 他干过什么坏事
You have no idea the things he's done.
我绝不会去救他 明白吗？
I am not rescuing him OK?
这次不会 以后也没门儿！
Not now, not ever!
我没让你去英雄救美男 小隔
Dah, you don't need to bromance him, Bulk.
你需要的是打败他！
You just need to beat him!
呃 什么？
Uh, what?
不救他 你就没机会揍他了
No rescue, no rematch.
走这边
This way.
信号就来自…
Readings coming from right...
…这里
... here.
打击的眼睛
Breakdown's eye.
是机械党
MECH.
你要干嘛？
What are you doing?
视觉接收器可能保存了最后收到的影像
The optic receptors might have retained the final image received.
你猜怎么着？
What do you know?
科学怪人又赢了
Weird science wins again.
哦…
Oh...
哎呀呀 擎天柱
Well, well, Optimus Prime.
很高兴又“亲眼”见到你了
A pleasure to "set eyes" on you again.
他把视学接收器改为双向传输了
He's converted the optics to a two-way feed.
你一定就是塞拉斯
And you must be Silas.
正是本人
In the flesh.
但由于我的俘虏不是你的人
But being that our captive is not one of yours.
我得承认
I have to admit
我以为来的会是…
I was expecting...
…威震天
... Megatron.
在当前状况下
In this circumstance
汽车人和霸天虎有了共同的敌人
Autobots and Decpticons share a common foe.
机械党跟你们那些敌人没有共同点！
MECH is anything but common.
我们的客人提供了大量 关于机械生命体的信息
Our guest is yielding quite a bit of information about your bio-mechanics
正如你们所见
as you can see.
可惜打击自己看不大清楚了
Although Breakdown himself can't see so well any more.
我们不怕你！
We don't fear you!
噢 你们早晚会怕的
Oh, but you should.
实际上 我强烈建议 你们别站得太死板了
In fact, I would strongly urge that you not stand your ground.
这是个陷阱！
It's a trap!
既然这样 你是不是该喊“出发”了？
Would this be a "roll out" kind of trap?
火速撤离！
Evacuate now!
好了 谁知道他们把打击的零件藏在哪儿了？
So, any idea where they're keeping the rest of Breakdown?
手术过程好看吗？
Enjoying the view?
真是讽刺 你的救星现在可能死无全尸了
Ironically your would-be rescuers may be in more pieces than you right now.
霸天虎没那么不堪一击！
Decpticons don't break that easy!
我可没说他们是霸天虎
Who said they were Decpticons?
那不可能
That doesn't make sense
汽车人怎么会来救我
Autobots wouldn't come to rescue me.
“马可”！
Marco!
你应该接着说“波罗”！
You're supposed to say "Polo"!
又来了个送死的
More grist for the mill.
今天是你的幸运日
It must be your lucky day.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
救你出去
Getting you outta here.
没错 我也觉得太离谱
Yea, I don't believe it either.
你还能走么？
Can you walk?
呃 应该能
Uh, I think so.
能跑么？
Can you run?
要死战到底 决不逃跑！
Never run when you can fight!
别用那玩意儿对着我 好么？
Just keep that thing pointed away from me, alright?
怪兽二人组杀过来喽！
Creature double feature coming at you!
你有逃跑的计划吗？
You have some sort of escape plan?
有 但不合你的口味
Yea, but you're not gonna like it.
隔板呼叫擎天柱
Bulkhead to Optimus
到我的坐标处集合
Rendezvous to my coordinates
我需要支援
I'm in need of backup.
长官 不明敌机正在接近
Sir, incoming bogies.
所有单位注意
All units
撤出战斗 执行欧米加方案
disengage and initiate Omega Protocols.
是你的援兵吗？
Your backup?
红蜘蛛指挥官！
Commander Starscream.
居然和敌人私通？打击啊
Counsulting with the enemy, Breakdown?
是隔板救我出来的
But Bulkhead got me out of there.
我的火种充满感激之情 汽车人
Many spark felt thanks, Autobot.
现在消灭他
Now destory him.
但是…
But you...
你打算过几天加入他们的队伍吗？
Do you plan on joining their ranks anytime soon?
不想吧？那就跟他们划清界限！
No? Then be done with them already!
很不幸 隔板
Tough break, Bulkhead
此恩来生再报
maybe the next life.
消灭他！啊！
Destory him! Ah!
这一锤送你们上路！
Hammer time!
来啊 我把你们全都砸成碎片！
Come on, I'll scrap all of you!
撤退！
Ahh... Retreat!
你单枪匹马独自迎敌 比上次还要鲁莽 隔板
Engaging the enemy on your own was even more foolish this time, Bulkhead.
但是
But
我很欣慰 你能顾全大局 营救自己的对头
I am honored that you saw fit to rescue your rival.
你真的比以前成长了许多
You have truely risen above yourself.
你们看到了吗
Did you see
我赢了打击 还用他的铁锤狠狠揍了他们一顿！
I beat Breakdown and bashed them all with his own hammer!
这次复赛我赢了！
I won the rematch!
神子一定会为你感到骄傲的
I'm sure Miko would be proud.
总有一天 你要还我一个人情 打击
One day, you will repay you debt to me, Breakdown
到时候 你可要选对立场！
the day it comes time to choose sides.
呃 在轮子和虎子之间吗？
Uh, between Bots and Cons?
在我本人和威震天之间
Between myself and Megatron.
顺便说一句
Incidentally
我建议你不要向威震天提起这次拯救行动
I suggest that Megatron never know of this rescue.
你也想让他觉得 是你自己打败那些小不点儿的
You do what him to think you overcame the puny humans on your own
没错吧？
don't you?
试验品逃走了
The test subject escaped
但我们及时清理了现场
but we managed to sanitize the location and transfer
并将刚刚得到的数据 转移到了另一处基地
most of the newly acquired data to another facility.
对试验品各关键部件的详细扫描
Our diagnostic scans of the subject's vital components
（Chimera 奇美拉  希腊神话中狮头、羊身、蛇尾的吐火怪物)
were thorough enough for us to initiate Project Chimera.
足以让我们启动奇美拉计划
（Chimera 奇美拉  希腊神话中狮头、羊身、蛇尾的吐火怪物)
The power of the living mechines will
这些活体机器的力量
不日之后
some day soon
将属于机械党！
belong to MECH.